<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Converted by db4-upgrade version 1.0 -->
<article xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" version="5.0">
	<xi:include xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="Article_Info.xml"/>
		<variablelist><info><title>Publican 4.2 Release Notes</title></info>

		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add iframe video support to DocBook5 HTML5</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, Publican used the <tag>&lt;embed&gt;</tag> tag to insert video content into documents. However, some browers did not support video represented this way when the video was served from another site. Publican now uses an <tag>&lt;iframe&gt;</tag> to embed video in pages, which works for video linked from other sites as well as video that's local to the document.  <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=752021">BZ#752021</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Stop calculating column width if no width is set</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, Publican would automatically set a column width for tables if no column width was set. That is, without specific instructions from an author, Publican would specify columns of equal size. This prevented browsers from resizing columns to fit content. Publican now sets a column width only if specified by the author. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1084860">BZ#1084860</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Simply styling of code, and admonitions in HTML5</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, Publican used elaborate markup to denote code samples and admonition. These approaches have now been replaced by coloured bars at the side of the text, to create a less intrusive approach. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1093498">BZ#1093498</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Added tip formatting</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican's common brand did not provide styles for the DocBook <tag>&lt;tip&gt;</tag> element. Now <tag>&lt;tip&gt;</tag> joins the other four element supported (<tag>&lt;note&gt;</tag>, <tag>&lt;important&gt;</tag>, and <tag>&lt;warning&gt;</tag>). <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1033830">BZ#1033830</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add "popper" to hide programlisting after 4 lines</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican 4.2 includes a new feature to increase the usability of documentation that includes long <tag>&lt;programlisting&gt;</tag>s. The <firstterm>popper</firstterm> hides <tag>&lt;programlisting&gt;</tag>s after their first four lines, and provides the reader with a control to expand the rest of the listing if they want to read it.  <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1088051">BZ#1088051</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Fix white space being removed from msgids when merging</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, Publican ignored leading whitespace in msgids when merging translations. Therefore, although the msgid was a correct representation of the XML, Publican would not replace the corresponding XML content with the msgstr. Publican now merges translated content with leading whitespace correctly. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1097090">BZ#1097090</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add code language switching</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican 4.2 includes a new feature to increase the usability of documentation that includes parallel samples of code in multiple programming languages. Any <tag>&lt;programlisting&gt;</tag>s grouped together in an <tag>&lt;informalexample role="switchery"&gt;</tag> element are presented to the reader in a single display area with tabs to switch between the various languages. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1092351">BZ#1092351</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Fix CDATA support</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, Publican did not ensure that CDATA was never escaped or resolved. For example, entities in CDATA were resolved when creating POT files. CDATA is now preserved throughout all code paths in Publican.  <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1101050">BZ#1101050</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add --showfuzzy to build options</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican 4.2 includes a new feature to assist in proof-reading documents in incomplete translations.  Previously, Publican would never use strings marked <firstterm>fuzzy</firstterm> when bulding a translated document. However, such strings might differ only slightly from a recent translation and still allow a translator to read a string in context. Adding the <option>--showfuzzy</option> option to a <command>publican build</command> command incorporates fuzzy strings tothether with completed translations. 
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Move PO manipulation to Locale::PO</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican now uses the <package>Locale::PO</package> module to perform manipulations on PO files, rather than handling these itself. 
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Fix inline "\n" not working in POT files for verbatim text</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, when the characters "\n" occurred in verbatim text, Publican would not escape them when incorporating them into msgids for POT files. This difference in msgid precluded accurate translation. The "\n" characters are now properly escaped. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1097091">BZ#1097091</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Fix images for DocBook 4 website callouts</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Callouts for code samples in DocBook 4 content have not worked in recent versions of Publican, displaying broken images instead. Publican 4.2 corrects the path to the brand assets, and adds CSS to make the icon visible. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1112899">BZ#1112899</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Remove newline after CDATA</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, any CDATA in a docunment would be followed by a newline. This behaviour is corected in Publican 4.2.<link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1110611">BZ#1110611</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add Markdown output</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican 4.2 provides a new output format: <literal>Markdown</literal>. Specify this format the same way as any other; with the <option>--formats</option> option when building a book. <link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1120455">BZ#1120455</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add external link support</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Publican 4.2 supports arbitrary links to be displayed alongside links to documents on the splash pages of a Publican-driven documentation site. Specify these links in the <filename>en-US/External_Links.xml</filename> file of a splash page package, in the format:
				</para>
<programlisting language="XML">&lt;simplelist&gt;
  &lt;member role="10" title="The Ways And Means Of Pants" href="https://pants.example.com" version="6"&gt;Pants in all thier glory!&lt;/member&gt;
&lt;/simplelist&gt;</programlisting>
				<para>
					<link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1123193">BZ#1123193</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
		<varlistentry>
			<term>Add &lt;th&gt; to translation block list</term>
			<listitem>
				<para>
					Previously, Publican omitted the HTML table element <tag>&lt;th&gt;</tag> from being processed into msgids in PO files, precluding the translation of the contents of these elements. Now Publican makes the contents of these elements available for translation.<link xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=1127462">BZ#1127462</link>
				</para>
			</listitem>
		</varlistentry>
	</variablelist>
	<xi:include xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="Revision_History.xml"/>
	<!-- index/ -->
</article>
